Hello friends Amazing Libas is again
present among you with a question
of tweet and as you are playing with us,
turning on some song, I am feeling very
good, now I am having a lot of fun, so here is my
second question for you today, so the second
question is that the entire your and null
expressway doing good deeds pet and phone
repeatedly saying what will you do call
videocon because its district village in any way will get angry
birds game where
you will find the number and name comes to n
and
that study so please let me read in Hindi that
if you are driving
your Dhundi at a speed of 180 kilometers per hour on an expressway
and in the middle of it your
phone is continuously moving, what will you do now, then the
first option is as per can practice is
important you order online to keep and
you have a teaspoon minute and maybe the button may be then
I should pick up, then you will
pick up the entire angry to talk will you
mute the phone because it is
directing you car
Your attention is getting distracted while operating it. Thirdly, if you will hear it
ringing, then there is another possibility
that you will get very angry that
it is disturbing you a lot. So what
else will you be afraid of or is it on them when you are
operating the curry. If you get a call,
please do that. And I would like to tell you again
that we are getting a lot of response on Twitter,
for that we are going to talk to
those who are weather and so
on our Twitter,
hello viewers who follow and
winners are also happening, so they are sharing it
in their tweets. Thank you. So, we
want to thank you very much on behalf of our team and our friends, in this way Amazon, that you are
adding to it in such a good way.
We thank you from the bottom of our hearts for that and
as your slogan is, you can use that. And
friends, I want to discuss a special topic. Till now,
our
professor from International University is there on
Click on Pay and he has done Children
and he was telling that why he
chose Children Shetty because and this is a
terrible thing in our country.  Now, just today night,
Rajasthan sent a message on an accident,
his nephew and small children were going to
drop them to school and they
collided with a tractor and both of them died, so
you think about them, you have
people in your house and you have our children, our children
die, friends, we do
not take all the necessary measures for their safety,
how do we take care of the complete safety of the children
in our house, we are taking so much care, if it gets cold then
we are making warning plates for them, installing
meters for them
and when a woman gets pregnant at that
age, we take care of them, we
explain to them so much that you should take care,
but he comes out and is on the road,
now why do we forget to take care of them, for this
we
took our matter very seriously today, he said that we send
our children to other places, at such a
time of great need, we said that we will
not make the school properly heated, take care of our children, until the
entire proper set up is done, we are
looking after the work in the school and
what are the arrangements for the children's safety.
We are seeing this because writing about playing and jumping is
meaningful but we spend all our
time outside falling twice and never giving way to the
vehicle in which we are going to
drop them but we do
not take care of their safety, friends this is very wrong
meaning our thinking and this is why it is not improving
and that is why you know that in India there are at least
10,000
children below the
age of 80 years who are
not lacking in themselves, they
cannot think about their safety, they are completely
dependent on their parents, they do
not even go out on their own, they are sitting with you,
trusting you and loving you,
so it becomes our double responsibility to take
care of their safety
and at the same time it is also the case that when you teach them
your speed and power limit from the very beginning,
they develop into good citizens in the future,
renewable road safety utility and at the same time they get
into the habit of playing, there are
safety equipments, these are the safety things
which we should follow.  They are their
role models, they
can learn only by acting like you, so if we
want to take care of the safety of our children, we
want our two real money players to be
safe, our time, our
future, our home, our future happiness, these
future struggles, they will flourish, they will be
well educated, declared their names, if they
win safely then that is the first
important question, after that they
will respect the girl, so we should also pay
attention to that so that our children can
flourish safely, their
safety is taken care of, we have to be a role model for them, so
friends, they have
appointed our team that now according to your login
people, according to the law,
you should protect your children, small
child, yourself and also him in case of an
accident, it is
necessary to make it the auspicious time for the
semen of your child,
how much is the value of his life, you are
putting your child in a situation in a room to remove ₹225, ₹500,
here I turn towards my child
2510 Home and policy related here he does it while
bringing clothes, we can introduce them to romance, we can get used to them, so
our
thinking, how we want to think,
what we give priority in our behavior, it
depends on us, there should be no
law, there should be any plan,
similarly it is also about seat belt,
you should take care of your safety, you should
subscribe to get all the vaccinations,
so please
concentrate on the safety of your children, we do not want to see this child
running in a street fight, you
definitely do not want to see your child playing
Kabaddi, you will think that someday your child goes out on the
road just like that and you do not even know and
then you have nothing to do except shedding tears,
so friends, these are all
medicines, he said that the
person should not do it, they should not use it, till now
every friend of our Nuskhe channel, our products, for protection, seat belt is our 30, which we should express
our frustrations every morning, so do
not forget to subscribe to our channel, friends, on the
other hand, from my friend
Shravan because now  We
need to think a little bit about safety, especially if we do it then we have
brought a lot of changes in the way, so the
money we are spending on
giving gifts to our friends, if it is new, then if there was a
person who why can't he do it for himself,
like
bread, then we should consider that safety as the most
important thing and that is the
safety of the child, it will become a good
imprinted input, safety will be a good investment, firstly, it will
also be used in his future, by
buying toys, by buying clothes, by buying something else, it may happen to
him
on holidays, but the thing is paint which is
child specialist, or helmet, he is
using it till the time he is using it, then
his safety is also ensured
and secondly, it is also getting into his habit
that yes, I have to take care of safety, I have to
use these safety equipment,
so we are helping in building our future more and
secondly, in this way we are also helping in the development of gas,
so whatever loss is being
incurred, that percentage is equal to the education budget,
every year we are busy in these accidents on the roads,
we also see that  We can sleep with that money
and how many times can it give infection,
how many means we can get, if we
remove the encroachment on it then how much means we can
adopt any insecurity thing with our husband and it is in white and there is no harm, now
how to do this because I know
many of you will understand and do this, so
now the question is, suppose you are
doing good kilometer per hour on phone bill
also, sensitive, difficult, distracting,
please log in to subscribe to our channel,
stop your Kwid car and tips to Amarendra Singh
signing off, please give me